ILGWU Health and Safety Department Records 5780/208
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Epidemiological studies, soft tissue disorders of upper limbs of women garment workers, Purnett, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Epidemiological studies, Steven Stellman Study, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Epidemiological studies, summer interns, Tufts University, 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Epidemiological studies, Tufts University School of Medicine, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Epidemiological studies, University of Massachusetts Amherst, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Ergonomic Standard, Advance Notice of Proposed Rulemaking, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Ergonomic Standard, Advance Notice of Proposed Rulemaking, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Ergonomic Standard, California draft standard, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Ergonomic Standard, California draft standard, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Ergonomic Standard, California standard, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Ergonomic Standard, California standard, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Ergonomic Standard, guidelines/regulations, 1986-1995 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Ergonomic Standard, materials, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Ergonomic Standard, materials, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Ergonomic Statistics, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Fire Protection Standard, 1980-1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Formaldehyde Standard, 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Formaldehyde Standard, 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Formaldehyde Standard, administrative, 1980-1991 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Formaldehyde Standard, articles and commentary, 1980-1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Formaldehyde Standard, legal activity, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Formaldehyde Standard, legal activity, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Formaldehyde Standard, legal activity, challenge, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Formaldehyde Standard, legal activity, challenge, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Formaldehyde Standard, legal activity, challenge brief and motion, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Formaldehyde Standard, legal activity, meetings, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Hazard Communication Standard, 1987-1992 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Hazard Communication Standard, inspection procedures, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Hazard Communication Standard, articles, 1984-1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Hazard Communication Standard, chemicals, 1977-1994 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Hazard Communication Standard, chemicals, 1977-1994 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Hazard Communication Standard, directives and interpretations of the courts, 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Hazard Communication Standard, handouts and training material, 1988-1995 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Hazard Communication Standard, information, 1986-1992 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Hazard Communication Standard, information, 1986-1992 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Hazard Communication Standard, Material Safety Date Sheets, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Hazard Communication Standard, Material Safety Data Sheets collected from garment industry, 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Lead exposure inspections and compliance, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Lockout/Tagout, 1980-1991 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Standards, 1989-1995 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Mount Sinai Medical Center, New York, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Mount Sinai Medical Center, Edlund, Eric, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Mount Sinai Medical Center, International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Health Center, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- National Institute of Occupational Safety and Health (NIOSH), Benzidine- based dyes, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- National Institute of Occupational Safety and Health (NIOSH), dyes, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- National Institute of Occupational Safety and Health (NIOSH) facts, health information, 1980-1992 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- National Institute of Occupational Safety and Health (NIOSH) health hazard evaluations, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- National Institute of Occupational Safety and Health (NIOSH) health hazard evaluations-new directions: NIOSH Dyes Hazard Pilot Project, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Occupational Safety and Health Review Commission, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Occupational Safety and Health Act, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) chart of area offices, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) complaint forms, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) general, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) miscellaneous commentary, 1989-1995 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) miscellaneous commentary, 1989-1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) penalties, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) record keeping, 1986-1995 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) reform, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) rights, 1978-1993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) statistics, 1979-1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) statistics, 1979-1993 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) statistics, accidents/injury statistics, 1987-1992 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) statistics, accidents/injury statistics, 1987-1992 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) statistics, New York state statistics, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Permissible Exposure Limits (PELs) Standard, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Respirator Standard, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Respirator Standard, protection (proposed rule), 1994 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Right-to-Know (RTK), general information, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Right-to-Know (RTK), Connecticut, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Right-to-Know (RTK), Illinois, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Right-to-Know (RTK), Maine, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Right-to-Know (RTK), Massachusetts, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Right-to-Know (RTK), New Jersey, 1983-1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Right-to-Know (RTK), New Jersey, 1983-1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Right-to-Know (RTK), New York, 1981-1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Right-to-Know (RTK), New York, 1981-1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Right-to-Know (RTK),Pennsylvania, 1983-1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Right-to-Know (RTK) state law chart, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Right-to-Know (RTK) miscellaneous states, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Standards, Canada, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- State law/ regulations, building codes, New York State, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- State law/ regulations, California State laws, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- State law/ regulations, Fire codes, city of New York, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- State law/ regulations, New York City health, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- State law/ regulations, state plans, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- State law/ regulations, sweatshop task force, 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Studies, Cancer Survey (Box 12, Folder 15)
  medical; no date
- Studies, California Garment Survey of Labor Standards, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Studies, Danish, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Studies, Quebec, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Top 200 Pilot Targeting Program, Maine, 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- walk around pay, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), Health and Safety Department, 1989- 1993 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), Health and Safety Department, 1989- 1993 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), Health and Safety Department, 1989- 1993 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), Health and Safety Department, miscellaneous articles, 1985-1995 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), Health and Safety Department, New York State, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), Health and Safety Department, Ohio, 1988- 1995 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), Standing Committee on Safety and Occupational Health, 1988-1995 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) worker memorial organizing packet, 1991- 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  posters
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Environmental Network, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Industrial Union Department (IUD), 1984- 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Industrial Union Department (IUD), 1984- 1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Industrial Union Department (IUD), 1984- 1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Industrial Union Department (IUD) Occupational Health and Safety Forum, 1986-1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Industrial Union Department (IUD), health and safety environmental issues in organizing and coordinated campaigns, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Industrial Union Department (IUD), health and safety environmental issues in organizing and coordinated campaigns, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Comite de Apoyo a los Trabajadores Agricola's (CATA) Farmworkers Support Committee, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Central Labor Rehabilitation Council, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Communications Workers of America, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Food and Allied Service Trades Department (FAST), 1980-1986 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, International Chemical Workers Union (ICWU), 1980-1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, International Molders and Allied Workers Union, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation (ITGLWF), 1983-1993 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation (ITGLWF), 1983-1993 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation (ITGLWF), 1989-1993 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Occupational Health Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Occupational Health Legal Rights Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Union Health Center, occupational disease survey, 1988-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, United Auto Workers (UAW), 1980-1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, United Auto Workers (UAW), 1980-1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, United Mine Workers (UMW), 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, United Steelworkers of America, 1979-1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Workers' Institute for Safety and Health, 1981-1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Workplace Health Fund, 1984-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Union Health and Safety Organizations, Workplace Health Fund, 1984-1992 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Danish Textile and Garment Union, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1983-1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1983-1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- International Labor Organization, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation (ITGLWF),administrative, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation (ITGLWF), administrative, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation (ITGLWF), administrative, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation (ITGLWF), general, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Saipan and Guam, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Soviet Union, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Zimbabwe, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Trainings, 1984-1990 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Business agent trainings (education), spring/fall, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- New Jersey trainings, fall, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Shop Rep Training (Local-23-25), winter/spring, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Midwest School for Women Workers, July 15-20, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Leadership training for Health and Safety Committee Members, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Midwest Region training, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Ergonomics Conference, Empire State College, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Union Health Center Conference, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Ergonomics Conference, Massachusetts, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Fire safety minutes and materials, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Fire safety minutes and materials, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Health and Safety Conference, New York City, March 20, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Fall River Conference, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Northeast program, Unity House, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Asbestos slideshow for stationary engineers, high-pressure plant tender and related titles (questionnaires) (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Chemicals, training material, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Chemicals, training material, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Contract negotiations and internal International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Ergonomics, 1990-1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- fact sheets (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hospital workers, 1978-1994 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Malden Mills fire, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Material Safety Data Sheets, chemicals, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Material Safety Data Sheets, samples and fact sheets, how to understand MSDS, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) Formaldehyde slide tape, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Respirators (Box 15, Folder 12)
- "Sanitation in the Garment Industry" Chinese translation, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- slide/tape program scripts, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- slide/tape program scripts, 1983-1994 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- slide tape programs, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Spanish, case studies or problems for small groups (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Reuniones como formarlo (Spanish) (Box 15, Folder 18)
- We Came to Work, Not to Die, conference, (Spanish), February 23, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Spanish, frio (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Spanish, Health and Safety Committee, functions for preparing for meeting (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Incendios (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Metales (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Monoxide de Carbano (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Occupational medicine, Spanish (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Plomo, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Reproductive hazards, (Spanish) (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Respiradores (Spanish) (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Right to Know, Spanish, noise, chemicals, hazard communication standard (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Ruido (Spanish) (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Sindrome del Tunel Carpiano (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Spanish slideshow script, 1984-1990 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Stress (Spanish) (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Talking Unionone-on-one, training materials, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Toxic hazards, 1991-1997 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Training activities, committee (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Training Material, 1988-1996 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Training Material, 1988-1996 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Training on backs and injuries, outlines and statistics, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Transparencies, originals (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Update: Health and Safety, 1983-1990 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Video Display Terminals, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Workers' Compensation, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Manual originals (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Manual originals (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Originals, includes Creole fact sheet (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Originals (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Originals, for pamphlets, fact sheets, and publications (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Update: Health and Safety, originals, 1985-1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Graphics, anatomy (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Graphics, 1981-1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Graphics, 1981-1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Graphics, fact sheets and manual, 1985-1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Graphics, 1985-1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)